var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "آبَائِنَا",
        "answer": "our forefathers",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "ābāinā",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبُونَا",
        "answer": "and our father",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "wa-abūnā",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبِي",
        "answer": "my father",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "abī",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا أَبَتِ",
        "answer": "O my father",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "yāabati",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "I will bring you",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "ātīkum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَاهَا",
        "answer": "he came (to) it",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "atāhā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "(had) come to them",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "atāhum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأْتُوا",
        "answer": "Then bring",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "fatū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "who could bring you",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "yatīkum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "who could bring you",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "yatīkum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We bestowed upon him",
        "pcklId": "449",
        "tlit": "ātaynāhu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We gave",
        "pcklId": "450",
        "tlit": "ātaynā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيَ",
        "answer": "he was given",
        "pcklId": "451",
        "tlit": "ūtiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيَ",
        "answer": "was given",
        "pcklId": "452",
        "tlit": "ūtiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيَ",
        "answer": "was given",
        "pcklId": "453",
        "tlit": "ūtiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "We gave them",
        "pcklId": "454",
        "tlit": "ātaynāhumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْتَوْنَ",
        "answer": "will be given",
        "pcklId": "455",
        "tlit": "yu'tawna",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have been given",
        "pcklId": "456",
        "tlit": "ūtītum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآتَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "And We gave him",
        "pcklId": "457",
        "tlit": "waātaynāhu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَاكَ",
        "answer": "Allah has given you",
        "pcklId": "458",
        "tlit": "ātāka",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيتُهُ",
        "answer": "I have been given it",
        "pcklId": "459",
        "tlit": "ūtītuhu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيَ",
        "answer": "has been given",
        "pcklId": "460",
        "tlit": "ūtiya",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتُوا",
        "answer": "were given",
        "pcklId": "461",
        "tlit": "ūtū",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْجُرَنِي",
        "answer": "you serve me",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tajuranī",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَأْجِرْهُ",
        "answer": "Hire him",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "is'tajir'hu",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَأْجَرْتَ",
        "answer": "you (can) hire",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "is'tajarta",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرَ",
        "answer": "(the) reward",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "ajra",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their reward",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "ajrahum",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَجَلَيْنِ",
        "answer": "(of) the two terms",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-ajalayni",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَجَلَ",
        "answer": "the term",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-ajala",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِحْدَاهُمَا",
        "answer": "one of the two women",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "iḥ'dāhumā",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِحْدَاهُمَا",
        "answer": "one of them",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "iḥ'dāhumā",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِحْدَى",
        "answer": "one",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "iḥ'dā",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخَذْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "So We seized him",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "fa-akhadhnāhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَتَّخِذَهُ",
        "answer": "we may take him",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "nattakhidhahu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "and the last",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "wal-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةُ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiratu",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةَ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirata",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "آخَرَ",
        "answer": "other",
        "pcklId": "245",
        "tlit": "ākhara",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَخِي",
        "answer": "And my brother",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "wa-akhī",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَخِيكَ",
        "answer": "through your brother",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "bi-akhīka",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأُخْتِهِ",
        "answer": "to his sister",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "li-ukh'tihi",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "[when]",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "but when",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "when behold",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "263",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "266",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْضِنَا",
        "answer": "our land",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "arḍinā",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "349",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "350",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "351",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "352",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "353",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "354",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "355",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "356",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "357",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "358",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "905",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one who",
        "pcklId": "906",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one who",
        "pcklId": "907",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "The one who",
        "pcklId": "908",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one who",
        "pcklId": "909",
        "tlit": "bi-alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "910",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "whom",
        "pcklId": "911",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those ",
        "pcklId": "912",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) those whom",
        "pcklId": "913",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "whom",
        "pcklId": "914",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "915",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "916",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "917",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "to those who",
        "pcklId": "918",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "919",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "He Who",
        "pcklId": "920",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهٍ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "ilāhin",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهِ",
        "answer": "(the) God",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "ilāhi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهٌ",
        "answer": "(is the) god",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "ilāhun",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهٌ",
        "answer": "(is the) god",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "ilāhun",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهًا",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "ilāhan",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "the Promise of Allah",
        "pcklId": "1983",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah wills",
        "pcklId": "1984",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and Allah",
        "pcklId": "1985",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1986",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "from Allah",
        "pcklId": "1987",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1988",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1989",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1990",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1991",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(to) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1992",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1993",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah made",
        "pcklId": "1994",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1995",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah made",
        "pcklId": "1996",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1997",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "(is) for Allah",
        "pcklId": "1998",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1999",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has given you",
        "pcklId": "2000",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has been good",
        "pcklId": "2001",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2002",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2003",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2004",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2005",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2006",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah had favored",
        "pcklId": "2007",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2008",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2009",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "[to]",
        "pcklId": "464",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكِ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "465",
        "tlit": "ilayki",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "466",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "467",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيَّ",
        "answer": "to me",
        "pcklId": "468",
        "tlit": "ilayya",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to yourselves",
        "pcklId": "469",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "470",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمَا",
        "answer": "to both of you",
        "pcklId": "471",
        "tlit": "ilaykumā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "at",
        "pcklId": "472",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْنَا",
        "answer": "to Us",
        "pcklId": "473",
        "tlit": "ilaynā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "474",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "475",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْنَا",
        "answer": "to us",
        "pcklId": "476",
        "tlit": "ilaynā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to it",
        "pcklId": "477",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "before You",
        "pcklId": "478",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "and to Him",
        "pcklId": "479",
        "tlit": "wa-ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "till",
        "pcklId": "480",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "till",
        "pcklId": "481",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "482",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "483",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "484",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "485",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "486",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "and to Him",
        "pcklId": "487",
        "tlit": "wa-ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتَمِرُونَ",
        "answer": "are taking counsel",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "yatamirūna",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَمْرَ",
        "answer": "the Commandment",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "l-amra",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْأَمْسِ",
        "answer": "the previous day",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bil-amsi",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْأَمْسِ",
        "answer": "yesterday",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "bil-amsi",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْأَمْسِ",
        "answer": "the day before",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "bil-amsi",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمِّ",
        "answer": "(the) mother",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ummi",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمِّ",
        "answer": "(of the) mother",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ummi",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمِّهِ",
        "answer": "his mother",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ummihi",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمِّهَا",
        "answer": "their mother (town)",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "ummihā",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَئِمَّةً",
        "answer": "leaders",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "a-immatan",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَئِمَّةً",
        "answer": "leaders",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "a-immatan",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّةً",
        "answer": "a group",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "ummatan",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّةٍ",
        "answer": "nation",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "ummatin",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَمَّا",
        "answer": "But as for",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "fa-ammā",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "who believe",
        "pcklId": "381",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "382",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "We believe",
        "pcklId": "383",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآمَنَ",
        "answer": "and believed",
        "pcklId": "384",
        "tlit": "waāmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَ",
        "answer": "believes",
        "pcklId": "385",
        "tlit": "āmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَمِينُ",
        "answer": "the trustworthy",
        "pcklId": "580",
        "tlit": "l-amīnu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمِنًا",
        "answer": "secure",
        "pcklId": "591",
        "tlit": "āminan",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the secure",
        "pcklId": "597",
        "tlit": "l-āminīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the believers",
        "pcklId": "786",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the believers",
        "pcklId": "787",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "آنَسَ",
        "answer": "he saw",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ānasa",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "آنَسْتُ",
        "answer": "[I] perceive",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ānastu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَهَا",
        "answer": "its people",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "ahlahā",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "ahli",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِهَا",
        "answer": "its people",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "ahlihā",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَهْلِهِ",
        "answer": "with his family",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "bi-ahlihi",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَهْلِهِ",
        "answer": "to his family",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "li-ahlihi",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "ahli",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَهْلُهَا",
        "answer": "while their people",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "wa-ahluhā",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُولَىٰ",
        "answer": "former",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-ūlā",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُولَىٰ",
        "answer": "the first",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "l-ūlā",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَوَّلِينَ",
        "answer": "our forefathers",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "l-awalīna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُولِي",
        "answer": "possessors of great strength",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "ulī",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلُ",
        "answer": "(the) family",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "ālu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتُ",
        "answer": "(are the) Verses",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "āyātu",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Through Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "258",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "with Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "259",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "260",
        "tlit": "āyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِكَ",
        "answer": "Your Verses",
        "pcklId": "261",
        "tlit": "āyātika",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "262",
        "tlit": "āyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) Verses",
        "pcklId": "263",
        "tlit": "āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتُبْدِي",
        "answer": "(to) disclosing",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "latub'dī",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَرَّأْنَا",
        "answer": "We declare our innocence",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "tabarranā",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُبَارَكَةِ",
        "answer": "blessed",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-mubārakati",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُرْهَانَانِ",
        "answer": "(are) two evidences",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "bur'hānāni",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُرْهَانَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your proof",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "bur'hānakum",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْسُطُ",
        "answer": "extends",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yabsuṭu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبَصُرَتْ",
        "answer": "So she watched",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fabaṣurat",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "tub'ṣirūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصَائِرَ",
        "answer": "(as) an enlightenment",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "baṣāira",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَطِرَتْ",
        "answer": "which exulted",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "baṭirat",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْطِشَ",
        "answer": "strike",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yabṭisha",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْعَثَ",
        "answer": "He (had) sent",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "yabʿatha",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after [what]",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهِمْ",
        "answer": "after them",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "baʿdihim",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبَغَىٰ",
        "answer": "but he oppressed",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "fabaghā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبْغِ",
        "answer": "seek",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "tabghi",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبْتَغِي",
        "answer": "we seek",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "nabtaghī",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِتَبْتَغُوا",
        "answer": "and that you may seek",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "walitabtaghū",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَابْتَغِ",
        "answer": "But seek",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "wa-ib'taghi",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبُقْعَةِ",
        "answer": "the place even",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-buq'ʿati",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَبْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "and more lasting",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wa-abqā",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَلَغَ",
        "answer": "he reached",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "balagha",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْنَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their sons",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "abnāahum",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنَتَيَّ",
        "answer": "(of) my daughters",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "ib'natayya",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْتٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a house",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "baytin",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْضَاءَ",
        "answer": "white",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "bayḍāa",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنِي",
        "answer": "(is) between me",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "baynī",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَيْنَكَ",
        "answer": "and between you",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "wabaynaka",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيِّنَاتٍ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "388",
        "tlit": "bayyinātin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُبِينِ",
        "answer": "the clear",
        "pcklId": "434",
        "tlit": "l-mubīni",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "clearly",
        "pcklId": "435",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "436",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٍ",
        "answer": "manifest",
        "pcklId": "437",
        "tlit": "mubīnin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَتْبَعْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "And We caused to follow them",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wa-atbaʿnāhum",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبَعَكُمَا",
        "answer": "follow you",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "ittabaʿakumā",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَتَّبِعَ",
        "answer": "so we (could have) followed",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "fanattabiʿa",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَّبِعْهُ",
        "answer": "that I may follow it",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "attabiʿ'hu",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّبِعُونَ",
        "answer": "they follow",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "yattabiʿūna",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبَعَ",
        "answer": "follows",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "ittabaʿa",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَتَّبِعِ",
        "answer": "we follow",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "nattabiʿi",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَتْلُو",
        "answer": "We recite",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "natlū",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتْلُو",
        "answer": "reciting",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "tatlū",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُتْلَىٰ",
        "answer": "it is recited",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "yut'lā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتْلُو",
        "answer": "reciting",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "yatlū",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتْمَمْتَ",
        "answer": "you complete",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "atmamta",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَابَ",
        "answer": "repented",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "tāba",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَمَرَاتُ",
        "answer": "fruits",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "thamarātu",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَمَانِيَ",
        "answer": "(for) eight",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "thamāniya",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَوَابُ",
        "answer": "(The) reward",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "thawābu",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَاوِيًا",
        "answer": "a dweller",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "thāwiyan",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَبَّارًا",
        "answer": "a tyrant",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "jabbāran",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُجْبَىٰ",
        "answer": "are brought",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yuj'bā",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَذْوَةٍ",
        "answer": "a burning wood",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "jadhwatin",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُجْرِمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the criminals",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "lil'muj'rimīna",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُجْرِمُونَ",
        "answer": "the criminals",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-muj'rimūna",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجْزِي",
        "answer": "We reward",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "najzī",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَجْزِيَكَ",
        "answer": "that he may reward you",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "liyajziyaka",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُجْزَى",
        "answer": "will be recompensed",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "yuj'zā",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلَ",
        "answer": "and made",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "wajaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَجْعَلَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and make them",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "wanajʿalahum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَجْعَلَهُمُ",
        "answer": "and make them",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "wanajʿalahumu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَجْعَلُ",
        "answer": "and We will make",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "wanajʿalu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاجْعَلْ",
        "answer": "and make",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "fa-ij'ʿal",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "And We made them",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnāhum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "Allah made",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "Allah made",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "He made",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجْعَلُهَا",
        "answer": "We assign it",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "najʿaluhā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَاعِلُوهُ",
        "answer": "and (will) make him",
        "pcklId": "344",
        "tlit": "wajāʿilūhu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمْعًا",
        "answer": "(in) accumulation",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "jamʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُنُبٍ",
        "answer": "a distance",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "junubin",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَانِبِ",
        "answer": "(the) direction",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "jānibi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِجَانِبِ",
        "answer": "on (the) side",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "bijānibi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِجَانِبِ",
        "answer": "at (the) side",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "bijānibi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَاحَكَ",
        "answer": "your hand",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "janāḥaka",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجُنُودَهُمَا",
        "answer": "and their hosts",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wajunūdahumā",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجُنُودَهُمَا",
        "answer": "and their hosts",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wajunūdahumā",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجُنُودُهُ",
        "answer": "and his hosts",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wajunūduhu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجُنُودَهُ",
        "answer": "and his hosts",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wajunūdahu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَانٌّ",
        "answer": "(were) a snake",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "jānnun",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَاهِلِينَ",
        "answer": "the ignorant",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-jāhilīna",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَبْتُمُ",
        "answer": "did you answer",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ajabtumu",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَجِيبُوا",
        "answer": "they respond",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "yastajībū",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَجِيبُوا",
        "answer": "they will respond",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "yastajībū",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَاءَ",
        "answer": "And came",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "wajāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَجَاءَتْهُ",
        "answer": "Then came to him",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "fajāathu",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُ",
        "answer": "he came to him",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "jāahu",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "jāahum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "has come",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُمُ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "jāahumu",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "comes",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "comes",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "comes",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَيْبِكَ",
        "answer": "your bosom",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "jaybika",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْبَبْتَ",
        "answer": "you love",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "aḥbabta",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "love",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "love",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِجَجٍ",
        "answer": "years",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "ḥijajin",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْذَرُونَ",
        "answer": "fearing",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yaḥdharūna",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحَرَّمْنَا",
        "answer": "And We had forbidden",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "waḥarramnā",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَمًا",
        "answer": "a sanctuary",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "ḥaraman",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْزَنِي",
        "answer": "grieve",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "taḥzanī",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْزَنَ",
        "answer": "she may grieve",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "taḥzana",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحَزَنًا",
        "answer": "and a grief",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "waḥazanan",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَحْسِنْ",
        "answer": "And do good",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wa-aḥsin",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنَ",
        "answer": "Allah has been good",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "aḥsana",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسَنًا",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "ḥasanan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَسَنَةِ",
        "answer": "with good ",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥasanati",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَسَنَةِ",
        "answer": "with a good (deed)",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥasanati",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْضَرِينَ",
        "answer": "those presented",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'ḍarīna",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَظٍّ",
        "answer": "(of) fortune",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ḥaẓẓin",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقَّ",
        "answer": "(has) come true",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "in truth",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقٌّ",
        "answer": "(is) true",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqun",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "right",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the truth",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقَّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُكْمًا",
        "answer": "wisdom",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "ḥuk'man",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُكْمُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Decision",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "l-ḥuk'mu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُكْمُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Decision",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "l-ḥuk'mu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَمْدُ",
        "answer": "(are due) all praises",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-ḥamdu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِينِ",
        "answer": "a time",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ḥīni",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْتَحْيِي",
        "answer": "and letting live",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "wayastaḥyī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةِ",
        "answer": "(of the) life",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayati",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةِ",
        "answer": "(of the) life",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayati",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةَ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayata",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتِحْيَاءٍ",
        "answer": "shyness",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "is'tiḥ'yāin",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِخَبَرٍ",
        "answer": "some information",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "bikhabarin",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاخْرُجْ",
        "answer": "so leave",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "fa-ukh'ruj",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَخَرَجَ",
        "answer": "So he left",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "fakharaja",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْرُجْ",
        "answer": "it will come forth",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "takhruj",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَخَرَجَ",
        "answer": "So he went forth",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "fakharaja",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَخَسَفْنَا",
        "answer": "Then We caused to swallow up",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fakhasafnā",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَخَسَفَ",
        "answer": "He would have caused it to swallow us",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "lakhasafa",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاطِئِينَ",
        "answer": "sinners",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "khāṭiīna",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَطْبُكُمَا",
        "answer": "(is the) matter with both of you",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "khaṭbukumā",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُتَخَطَّفْ",
        "answer": "we would be swept",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "nutakhaṭṭaf",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْلُقُ",
        "answer": "creates",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "yakhluqu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِفْتِ",
        "answer": "you fear",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "khif'ti",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخَافِي",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "takhāfī",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخَفْ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "takhaf",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخَفْ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "takhaf",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخَافُ",
        "answer": "and I fear",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "fa-akhāfu",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَافُ",
        "answer": "I fear",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "akhāfu",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَائِفًا",
        "answer": "fearful",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "khāifan",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَائِفًا",
        "answer": "fearing",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "khāifan",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَخْتَارُ",
        "answer": "and chooses",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wayakhtāru",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٍ",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "khayrin",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرَ",
        "answer": "(the) best",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "khayra",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) better",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخِيَرَةُ",
        "answer": "the choice",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "l-khiyaratu",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُدْبِرًا",
        "answer": "(in) flight",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "mud'biran",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَدَخَلَ",
        "answer": "And he entered",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "wadakhala",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَدْرَءُونَ",
        "answer": "and they repel",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wayadraūna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْعُوكَ",
        "answer": "calls you",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "yadʿūka",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "inviting",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "yadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْعُوا",
        "answer": "Call",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "id'ʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَدَعَوْهُمْ",
        "answer": "And they will call them",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "fadaʿawhum",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَادْعُ",
        "answer": "And invite (people)",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "wa-ud'ʿu",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُ",
        "answer": "invoke",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "tadʿu",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدُلُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "direct you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "adullukum",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "world",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "the world",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدَّارِ",
        "answer": "the good end in the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-dāri",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدَّارَ",
        "answer": "the home",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "l-dāra",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِدَارِهِ",
        "answer": "and his home",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "wabidārihi",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدَّارُ",
        "answer": "the Home",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-dāru",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِمُ",
        "answer": "besides them",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "dūnihimu",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُذَبِّحُ",
        "answer": "slaughtering",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yudhabbiḥu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَذَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "remember",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "yatadhakkarūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَذَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "remember",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "yatadhakkarūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَذَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "remember",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "yatadhakkarūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُنُوبِهِمُ",
        "answer": "their sins",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "dhunūbihimu",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذُودَانِ",
        "answer": "keeping back",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tadhūdāni",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَآهَا",
        "answer": "he saw it",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "raāhā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَأَوُا",
        "answer": "and they will see",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "wara-awū",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَأَيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "Have you seen",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "ara-aytum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَأَيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "Have you seen",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "ara-aytum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُرِيَ",
        "answer": "and show",
        "pcklId": "296",
        "tlit": "wanuriya",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "613",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "614",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "615",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "616",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "617",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّ",
        "answer": "(the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "618",
        "tlit": "rabbu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "619",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "620",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "621",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "622",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "623",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّنَا",
        "answer": "our Lord",
        "pcklId": "624",
        "tlit": "rabbinā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "625",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "626",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "And your Lord",
        "pcklId": "627",
        "tlit": "warabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "And your Lord",
        "pcklId": "628",
        "tlit": "warabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "My Lord",
        "pcklId": "629",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "630",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "631",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَطْنَا",
        "answer": "We strengthened",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "rabaṭnā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرْجَعُونَ",
        "answer": "will be returned",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "yur'jaʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْجَعُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be returned",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "tur'jaʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْجَعُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be returned",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "tur'jaʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجُلَيْنِ",
        "answer": "two men",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "rajulayni",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجُلٌ",
        "answer": "a man",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "rajulun",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرْجُو",
        "answer": "expecting",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "tarjū",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَحْمَةً",
        "answer": "and mercy",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "waraḥmatan",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَةً",
        "answer": "(as) a mercy",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "raḥmatan",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Mercy",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "raḥmatihi",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَةً",
        "answer": "(as) a mercy",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "raḥmatan",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحِيمُ",
        "answer": "the Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "296",
        "tlit": "l-raḥīmu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِدْءًا",
        "answer": "(as) a helper",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "rid'an",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَدَدْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "So We restored him",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "faradadnāhu",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَادُّوهُ",
        "answer": "(will) restore him",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "rāddūhu",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَرَادُّكَ",
        "answer": "(will) surely take you back",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "larādduka",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَزَقْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "We have provided them",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "razaqnāhum",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِزْقًا",
        "answer": "a provision",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "riz'qan",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّزْقَ",
        "answer": "the provision",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "l-riz'qa",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَرْسِلْهُ",
        "answer": "so send him",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "fa-arsil'hu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْتَ",
        "answer": "You sent",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "arsalta",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولًا",
        "answer": "a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "353",
        "tlit": "rasūlan",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولًا",
        "answer": "a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "354",
        "tlit": "rasūlan",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُرْسِلِينَ",
        "answer": "the Senders",
        "pcklId": "472",
        "tlit": "mur'silīna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلِينَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "497",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salīna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلِينَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "498",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salīna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْضِعِيهِ",
        "answer": "Suckle him",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "arḍiʿīhi",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَرَاضِعَ",
        "answer": "the wet nurses",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-marāḍiʿa",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّعَاءُ",
        "answer": "the shepherds",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-riʿāu",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَرَقَّبُ",
        "answer": "(and) was vigilant",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yataraqqabu",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَرَقَّبُ",
        "answer": "(and) vigilant",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yataraqqabu",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّهْبِ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-rahbi",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "And We wanted",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "wanurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَادَ",
        "answer": "he wanted",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "arāda",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "Do you intend",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "aturīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "you want",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "turīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "you want",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "turīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "[I] wish",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "urīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "I wish",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "urīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُونَ",
        "answer": "desire",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "yurīdūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُونَ",
        "answer": "desire",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "yurīdūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَزْعُمُونَ",
        "answer": "claim",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "tazʿumūna",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَزْعُمُونَ",
        "answer": "claim",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "tazʿumūna",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزِينَتُهَا",
        "answer": "and its adornment",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "wazīnatuhā",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "زِينَتِهِ",
        "answer": "his adornment",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "zīnatihi",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسْأَلُ",
        "answer": "will be questioned",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "yus'alu",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَسَاءَلُونَ",
        "answer": "will not ask one another",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "yatasāalūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَ",
        "answer": "Glory be",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥāna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبِيلِ",
        "answer": "way",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "l-sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِحْرٌ",
        "answer": "a magic",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "siḥ'run",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِحْرَانِ",
        "answer": "Two magic (works)",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "siḥ'rāni",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَرْمَدًا",
        "answer": "continuous",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "sarmadan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَرْمَدًا",
        "answer": "continuous",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "sarmadan",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْعَىٰ",
        "answer": "running",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yasʿā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْقُونَ",
        "answer": "watering",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yasqūna",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسْقِي",
        "answer": "We cannot water",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "nasqī",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَقَىٰ",
        "answer": "So he watered",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "fasaqā",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَقَيْتَ",
        "answer": "you watered",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "saqayta",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُسْكَنْ",
        "answer": "have been inhabited",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "tus'kan",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْكُنُونَ",
        "answer": "(for) you (to) rest",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "taskunūna",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَسْكُنُوا",
        "answer": "that you may rest",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "litaskunū",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَاكِنُهُمْ",
        "answer": "(are) their dwellings",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "masākinuhum",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُلْطَانًا",
        "answer": "an authority",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "sul'ṭānan",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْلُكْ",
        "answer": "Insert",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "us'luk",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلَامٌ",
        "answer": "Peace (be)",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "salāmun",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْلِمِينَ",
        "answer": "Muslims",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "mus'limīna",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِعْنَا",
        "answer": "we heard",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "samiʿ'nā",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِعُوا",
        "answer": "they hear",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "samiʿū",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْمَعُونَ",
        "answer": "you hear",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "tasmaʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُوءٍ",
        "answer": "any harm",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "sūin",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّيِّئَةَ",
        "answer": "the evil",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "l-sayi-ata",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالسَّيِّئَةِ",
        "answer": "with an evil (deed)",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "bil-sayi-ati",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّيِّئَاتِ",
        "answer": "the evil (deeds)",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "l-sayiāti",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْتَوَىٰ",
        "answer": "and became mature",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "wa-is'tawā",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوَاءَ",
        "answer": "(to the) sound",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "sawāa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَارَ",
        "answer": "and was traveling",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wasāra",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّجَرَةِ",
        "answer": "the tree",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-shajarati",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَنَشُدُّ",
        "answer": "We will strengthen",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "sanashuddu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشُدَّهُ",
        "answer": "his full strength",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ashuddahu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَدُّ",
        "answer": "(were) stronger",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ashaddu",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُشْرِكُونَ",
        "answer": "they associate (with Him)",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "yush'rikūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُرَكَائِيَ",
        "answer": "(are) My partners",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "shurakāiya",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُرَكَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your partners",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "shurakāakum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُرَكَائِيَ",
        "answer": "(are) My partners",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "shurakāiya",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكِينَ",
        "answer": "the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikīna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاطِئِ",
        "answer": "(the) side",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "shāṭi-i",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانِ",
        "answer": "(of) Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭāni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْعُرُونَ",
        "answer": "perceive",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yashʿurūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْعُرُونَ",
        "answer": "perceive",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yashʿurūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشُقَّ",
        "answer": "make it difficult",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ashuqqa",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْكُرُونَ",
        "answer": "be grateful",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "tashkurūna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِيدًا",
        "answer": "a witness",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "shahīdan",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّاهِدِينَ",
        "answer": "the witnesses",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "l-shāhidīna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "Allah wills",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "things",
        "pcklId": "417",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "things",
        "pcklId": "418",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "419",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْخٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a very old man",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "shaykhun",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِيَعًا",
        "answer": "(into) sects",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "shiyaʿan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِيعَتِهِ",
        "answer": "his party",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "shīʿatihi",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِيعَتِهِ",
        "answer": "his party",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "shīʿatihi",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصْبَحَ",
        "answer": "And became",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣbaḥa",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَصْبَحَ",
        "answer": "In the morning he was",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "fa-aṣbaḥa",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصْبَحَ",
        "answer": "And began",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣbaḥa",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَبَرُوا",
        "answer": "they are patient",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ṣabarū",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّابِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(to) the patient ones",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "l-ṣābirūna",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصُدُّنَّكَ",
        "answer": "avert you",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "yaṣuddunnaka",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُصْدِرَ",
        "answer": "take away",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yuṣ'dira",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "صُدُورُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their breasts",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ṣudūruhum",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُصَدِّقُنِي",
        "answer": "who will confirm me",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "yuṣaddiqunī",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "truthful",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَرْحًا",
        "answer": "a lofty tower",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṣarḥan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَصْرِخُهُ",
        "answer": "cried out to him for help",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yastaṣrikhuhu",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥīna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِحًا",
        "answer": "righteousness",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "ṣāliḥan",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِحًا",
        "answer": "righteous (deeds)",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "ṣāliḥan",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُصْلِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the reformers",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "l-muṣ'liḥīna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَصْطَلُونَ",
        "answer": "warm yourselves",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "taṣṭalūna",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُصِيبَهُمْ",
        "answer": "struck them",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "tuṣībahum",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصِيبَةٌ",
        "answer": "a disaster",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "muṣībatun",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَضْعِفُ",
        "answer": "oppressing",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yastaḍʿifu",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتُضْعِفُوا",
        "answer": "were oppressed",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "us'tuḍ'ʿifū",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَضَلَّ",
        "answer": "and (will be) lost",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "waḍalla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَضَلُّ",
        "answer": "(is) more astray",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "aḍallu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَالٍ",
        "answer": "an error",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "ḍalālin",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُضِلٌّ",
        "answer": "one who misleads",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "muḍillun",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاضْمُمْ",
        "answer": "And draw",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-uḍ'mum",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِضِيَاءٍ",
        "answer": "light",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "biḍiyāin",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَطَّلِعُ",
        "answer": "I may look",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "aṭṭaliʿu",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطُّورِ",
        "answer": "(of) Mount Tur",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-ṭūri",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطُّورِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Tur",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-ṭūri",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَائِفَةً",
        "answer": "a group",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ṭāifatan",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَطَاوَلَ",
        "answer": "and prolonged",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "fataṭāwala",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطِّينِ",
        "answer": "the clay",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-ṭīni",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظِّلِّ",
        "answer": "the shade",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "l-ẓili",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمْتُ",
        "answer": "[I] have wronged",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "ẓalamtu",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "252",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "253",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَالِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(were) wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "254",
        "tlit": "ẓālimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "301",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "302",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "303",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَظُنُّهُ",
        "answer": "[I] think that he",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "la-aẓunnuhu",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَظَنُّوا",
        "answer": "and they thought",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "waẓannū",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَظَاهَرَا",
        "answer": "supporting each other",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "taẓāharā",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَهِيرًا",
        "answer": "a supporter",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "ẓahīran",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَهِيرًا",
        "answer": "an assistant",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "ẓahīran",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْبُدُونَ",
        "answer": "worship us",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "yaʿbudūna",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "His slaves",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "ʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوًّا",
        "answer": "an enemy",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwan",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوِّهِ",
        "answer": "his enemy",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwihi",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوِّهِ",
        "answer": "his enemy",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwihi",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوٌّ",
        "answer": "(is) an enemy ",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwun",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوٌّ",
        "answer": "an enemy",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwun",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُدْوَانَ",
        "answer": "injustice",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "ʿud'wāna",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابَ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْرَضُوا",
        "answer": "they turn away",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "aʿraḍū",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَسَىٰ",
        "answer": "perhaps",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ʿasā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَسَىٰ",
        "answer": "Perhaps",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ʿasā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَسَىٰ",
        "answer": "then perhaps",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "faʿasā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَشْرًا",
        "answer": "ten",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ʿashran",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْعُصْبَةِ",
        "answer": "a company (of men)",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "bil-ʿuṣ'bati",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَصَاكَ",
        "answer": "your staff",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ʿaṣāka",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَضُدَكَ",
        "answer": "your arm",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ʿaḍudaka",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٍ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmin",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعَقِّبْ",
        "answer": "return",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yuʿaqqib",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاقِبَةُ",
        "answer": "the good end in the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ʿāqibatu",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاقِبَةُ",
        "answer": "(the) end",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ʿāqibatu",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْعَاقِبَةُ",
        "answer": "And the good end",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "wal-ʿāqibatu",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "you use intellect",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "taʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِتَعْلَمَ",
        "answer": "and that she would know",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "walitaʿlama",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِمْتُ",
        "answer": "I know",
        "pcklId": "258",
        "tlit": "ʿalim'tu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْلَمْ",
        "answer": "then know",
        "pcklId": "259",
        "tlit": "fa-iʿ'lam",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "260",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows",
        "pcklId": "261",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَلِمُوا",
        "answer": "Then they will know",
        "pcklId": "262",
        "tlit": "faʿalimū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمْ",
        "answer": "he know",
        "pcklId": "263",
        "tlit": "yaʿlam",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) most knowing",
        "pcklId": "445",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "knows best",
        "pcklId": "474",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) most knowing",
        "pcklId": "475",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "523",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعِلْمًا",
        "answer": "and knowledge",
        "pcklId": "619",
        "tlit": "waʿil'man",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمٍ",
        "answer": "(of) knowledge",
        "pcklId": "620",
        "tlit": "ʿil'min",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِلْمَ",
        "answer": "the knowledge",
        "pcklId": "621",
        "tlit": "l-ʿil'ma",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُعْلِنُونَ",
        "answer": "they declare",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yuʿ'linūna",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلَا",
        "answer": "exalted himself",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ʿalā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَعَالَىٰ",
        "answer": "and High is He",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wataʿālā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُلُوًّا",
        "answer": "exaltedness",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "ʿuluwwan",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعُمُرُ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "l-ʿumuru",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلَ",
        "answer": "and did",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "waʿamila",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلَ",
        "answer": "and does",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "waʿamila",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "ʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمَلِ",
        "answer": "(the) deed",
        "pcklId": "318",
        "tlit": "ʿamali",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَالُنَا",
        "answer": "our deeds",
        "pcklId": "319",
        "tlit": "aʿmālunā",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَالُكُمْ",
        "answer": "your deeds",
        "pcklId": "320",
        "tlit": "aʿmālukum",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَمِيَتْ",
        "answer": "But (will) be obscure",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "faʿamiyat",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "(is) with",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدِي",
        "answer": "I have",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "ʿindī",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدِكَ",
        "answer": "you",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "ʿindika",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدِهِ",
        "answer": "from Him",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "ʿindihi",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدِنَا",
        "answer": "from Us",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "ʿindinā",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدِ",
        "answer": "from Allah",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "ʿindi",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعَادٍ",
        "answer": "a place of return",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "maʿādin",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعِيشَتَهَا",
        "answer": "(in) its means of livelihood",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "maʿīshatahā",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَيْنٍ",
        "answer": "(of the) eye",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ʿaynin",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَيْنُهَا",
        "answer": "her eye",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ʿaynuhā",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَرْبِيِّ",
        "answer": "western",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-gharbiyi",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاغْفِرْ",
        "answer": "so forgive",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "fa-igh'fir",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَغَفَرَ",
        "answer": "Then He forgave",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "faghafara",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَفُورُ",
        "answer": "the Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "l-ghafūru",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَفْلَةٍ",
        "answer": "(of) inattention",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ghaflatin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَالِبُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) be the dominant",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-ghālibūna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَغَاثَهُ",
        "answer": "And called him for help",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "fa-is'taghāthahu",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَوَيْنَا",
        "answer": "we were astray",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ghawaynā",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغْوَيْنَا",
        "answer": "we led astray",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "aghwaynā",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغْوَيْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "We led them astray",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "aghwaynāhum",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَغَوِيٌّ",
        "answer": "(are) surely a deviator",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "laghawiyyun",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرِ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "ghayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرِي",
        "answer": "other than me",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "ghayrī",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "bighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "bighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرُ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "ghayru",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرُ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "ghayru",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "فُؤَادُ",
        "answer": "(the) heart",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "fuādu",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِئَةٍ",
        "answer": "group",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "fi-atin",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَفَاتِحَهُ",
        "answer": "(the) keys of it",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "mafātiḥahu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْرَحْ",
        "answer": "exult",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "tafraḥ",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَرِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the exultant",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-fariḥīna",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَضَ",
        "answer": "ordained",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "faraḍa",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَارِغًا",
        "answer": "empty",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "fārighan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْتَرُونَ",
        "answer": "invent",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "yaftarūna",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُفْتَرًى",
        "answer": "invented",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "muf'taran",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَسَادَ",
        "answer": "corruption",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "l-fasāda",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَادًا",
        "answer": "corruption",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "fasādan",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُفْسِدِينَ",
        "answer": "the corrupters",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-muf'sidīna",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُفْسِدِينَ",
        "answer": "the corrupters",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "l-muf'sidīna",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسِقِينَ",
        "answer": "defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "fāsiqīna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفْصَحُ",
        "answer": "(is) more eloquent",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "afṣaḥu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلِهِ",
        "answer": "His Bounty",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "faḍlihi",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(in) need",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "faqīrun",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُفْلِحُ",
        "answer": "will be successful",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "yuf'liḥu",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُفْلِحُ",
        "answer": "will succeed",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "yuf'liḥu",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُفْلِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the successful ones",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-muf'liḥīna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَقْبُوحِينَ",
        "answer": "the despised",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-maqbūḥīna",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقْبِلْ",
        "answer": "Draw near",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "aqbil",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكَ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "qablika",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِ",
        "answer": "before it",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "qablihi",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِ",
        "answer": "before it",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "qablihi",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِ",
        "answer": "before him",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "qablihi",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْتُلُوهُ",
        "answer": "kill him",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "taqtulūhu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْتُلَنِي",
        "answer": "kill me",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "taqtulanī",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَتَلْتَ",
        "answer": "you killed",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "qatalta",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَقْتُلُوكَ",
        "answer": "to kill you",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "liyaqtulūka",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَتَلْتُ",
        "answer": "I killed",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "qataltu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقْتُلُونِ",
        "answer": "they will kill me",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "yaqtulūni",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقْتَتِلَانِ",
        "answer": "fighting each other",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "yaqtatilāni",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقْدِرُ",
        "answer": "and restricts it",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wayaqdiru",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدَّمَتْ",
        "answer": "had sent forth",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "qaddamat",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنَ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "l-qur'āna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقَرَّ",
        "answer": "might be comforted",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "taqarra",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرَّتُ",
        "answer": "A comfort",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "qurratu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرُونَ",
        "answer": "the generations",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-qurūna",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرُونًا",
        "answer": "generations",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "qurūnan",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرُونِ",
        "answer": "the generations",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "l-qurūni",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْيَةٍ",
        "answer": "a town",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "qaryatin",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرَىٰ",
        "answer": "the towns",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "l-qurā",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرَىٰ",
        "answer": "the towns",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "l-qurā",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُصِّيهِ",
        "answer": "Follow him",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "quṣṣīhi",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَصَّ",
        "answer": "and narrated",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "waqaṣṣa",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَصَصَ",
        "answer": "the story",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-qaṣaṣa",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقْصَى",
        "answer": "(the) farthest end",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "aqṣā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَضَىٰ",
        "answer": "and killed him",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "faqaḍā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَضَيْتُ",
        "answer": "I complete",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "qaḍaytu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَضَىٰ",
        "answer": "Musa fulfilled",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "qaḍā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَضَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We decreed",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "qaḍaynā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلْبِهَا",
        "answer": "her heart",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "qalbihā",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "a little",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَتِ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "1144",
        "tlit": "waqālati",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَتْ",
        "answer": "And she said",
        "pcklId": "1145",
        "tlit": "waqālat",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالَتْ",
        "answer": "so she said",
        "pcklId": "1146",
        "tlit": "faqālat",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1147",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1148",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1149",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "1150",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "1151",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1152",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1153",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "1154",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1155",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَتَا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "1156",
        "tlit": "qālatā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالَ",
        "answer": "and said",
        "pcklId": "1157",
        "tlit": "faqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَتْ",
        "answer": "She said",
        "pcklId": "1158",
        "tlit": "qālat",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "1159",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَتْ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "1160",
        "tlit": "qālat",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1161",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1162",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَقُولُ",
        "answer": "we say",
        "pcklId": "1163",
        "tlit": "naqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1164",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1165",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1166",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "1167",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And Musa said",
        "pcklId": "1168",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And Firaun said",
        "pcklId": "1169",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "and they would say",
        "pcklId": "1170",
        "tlit": "fayaqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "1171",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "1172",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they said",
        "pcklId": "1173",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1174",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "1175",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "and say",
        "pcklId": "1176",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they say",
        "pcklId": "1177",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَقُولُ",
        "answer": "and say",
        "pcklId": "1178",
        "tlit": "fayaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "(Will) say",
        "pcklId": "1179",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقِيلَ",
        "answer": "And it will be said",
        "pcklId": "1180",
        "tlit": "waqīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَقُولُ",
        "answer": "and say",
        "pcklId": "1181",
        "tlit": "fayaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1182",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1183",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَقُولُ",
        "answer": "and say",
        "pcklId": "1184",
        "tlit": "fayaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقُلْنَا",
        "answer": "and We will say",
        "pcklId": "1185",
        "tlit": "faqul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "1186",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "1187",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "1188",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "But said",
        "pcklId": "1189",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "(to) say",
        "pcklId": "1190",
        "tlit": "yaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1191",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْلَ",
        "answer": "the Word",
        "pcklId": "1681",
        "tlit": "l-qawla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْلُ",
        "answer": "the Word",
        "pcklId": "1682",
        "tlit": "l-qawlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "375",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the people ",
        "pcklId": "376",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the people ",
        "pcklId": "377",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "378",
        "tlit": "qawman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "379",
        "tlit": "qawman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the people ",
        "pcklId": "380",
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "381",
        "tlit": "qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمُهُ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "382",
        "tlit": "qawmuhu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "383",
        "tlit": "qawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "533",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "534",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "535",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "536",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "537",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوِيُّ",
        "answer": "(is) the strong",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-qawiyu",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُوَّةِ",
        "answer": "possessors of great strength",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-quwati",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُوَّةً",
        "answer": "(in) strength",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "quwwatan",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْتَكْبَرَ",
        "answer": "And he was arrogant",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "wa-is'takbara",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبِيرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a very old man",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "kabīrun",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Book",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Scripture",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكِتَابٍ",
        "answer": "a Book",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "bikitābin",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Scripture",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابُ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "l-kitābu",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "most of them",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "aktharahum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "most of them",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "aktharahum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَكْثَرُ",
        "answer": "and greater",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "wa-aktharu",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُكَذِّبُونِ",
        "answer": "they will deny me",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "yukadhibūni",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَاذِبِينَ",
        "answer": "the liars",
        "pcklId": "245",
        "tlit": "l-kādhibīna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْفُرُوا",
        "answer": "they disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "yakfurū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "462",
        "tlit": "kāfirūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرُونَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "463",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "to the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "464",
        "tlit": "lil'kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْفُلُونَهُ",
        "answer": "who will rear him",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yakfulūnahu",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلٍّ",
        "answer": "in all",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "bikullin",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "(of) all",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُّ",
        "answer": "Every",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "kullu",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُنُوزِ",
        "answer": "the treasures",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-kunūzi",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُكِنُّ",
        "answer": "conceals",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tukinnu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَادَتْ",
        "answer": "she was near",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "kādat",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "898",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "899",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَكُونَ",
        "answer": "so that he might become",
        "pcklId": "900",
        "tlit": "liyakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "901",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَكُونَ",
        "answer": "so that she would be",
        "pcklId": "902",
        "tlit": "litakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكُونَ",
        "answer": "I will be",
        "pcklId": "903",
        "tlit": "akūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونَ",
        "answer": "you become",
        "pcklId": "904",
        "tlit": "takūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونَ",
        "answer": "you be",
        "pcklId": "905",
        "tlit": "takūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "are",
        "pcklId": "906",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونُ",
        "answer": "will be",
        "pcklId": "907",
        "tlit": "takūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "908",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتَ",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "909",
        "tlit": "kunta",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتَ",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "910",
        "tlit": "kunta",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتَ",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "911",
        "tlit": "kunta",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "[We] were",
        "pcklId": "912",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتَ",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "913",
        "tlit": "kunta",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَكُونَ",
        "answer": "and we (would) have been",
        "pcklId": "914",
        "tlit": "wanakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "915",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "[we] were",
        "pcklId": "916",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنَّا",
        "answer": "And indeed, [We]",
        "pcklId": "917",
        "tlit": "wakunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "918",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "We would be",
        "pcklId": "919",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used (to)",
        "pcklId": "920",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used (to)",
        "pcklId": "921",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "had been",
        "pcklId": "922",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونَ",
        "answer": "he will be",
        "pcklId": "923",
        "tlit": "yakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "they have",
        "pcklId": "924",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used (to)",
        "pcklId": "925",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used (to)",
        "pcklId": "926",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "927",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "928",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "929",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used (to)",
        "pcklId": "930",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتَ",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "931",
        "tlit": "kunta",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونَنَّ",
        "answer": "be",
        "pcklId": "932",
        "tlit": "takūnanna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونَنَّ",
        "answer": "be",
        "pcklId": "933",
        "tlit": "takūnanna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكَانَهُ",
        "answer": "his position",
        "pcklId": "1377",
        "tlit": "makānahu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَدُنَّا",
        "answer": "Us",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ladunnā",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِسَانًا",
        "answer": "(in) speech",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "lisānan",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَعْنَةً",
        "answer": "a curse",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "laʿnatan",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّغْوَ",
        "answer": "vain talk",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-laghwa",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالْتَقَطَهُ",
        "answer": "Then picked him up",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fal-taqaṭahu",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُلَقَّاهَا",
        "answer": "it is granted",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "yulaqqāhā",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَلْقِيهِ",
        "answer": "then cast him",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "fa-alqīhi",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلْقِ",
        "answer": "throw",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "alqi",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُلْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "would be sent down",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "yul'qā",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "تِلْقَاءَ",
        "answer": "towards",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "til'qāa",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَاقِيهِ",
        "answer": "(will) meet it",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "lāqīhi",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلَ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "al-layla",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِلَيْلٍ",
        "answer": "night",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "bilaylin",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلَ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "al-layla",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَتَّعْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We provided him",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "mattaʿnāhu",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَمَتَاعُ",
        "answer": "(is) an enjoyment",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "famatāʿu",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَتَاعَ",
        "answer": "enjoyment",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "matāʿa",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلَ",
        "answer": "(the) like",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "mith'la",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلَ",
        "answer": "(the) like",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "mith'la",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَدِينَةَ",
        "answer": "the city",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-madīnata",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَدِينَةِ",
        "answer": "the city",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-madīnati",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَدِينَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the city",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-madīnati",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "امْرَأَتُ",
        "answer": "(the) wife",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "im'ra-atu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "امْرَأَتَيْنِ",
        "answer": "two women",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "im'ra-atayni",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرَّتَيْنِ",
        "answer": "twice",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "marratayni",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمْشِي",
        "answer": "walking",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "tamshī",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "امْكُثُوا",
        "answer": "Stay here",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "um'kuthū",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُمَكِّنَ",
        "answer": "And [We] establish",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wanumakkina",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُمَكِّنْ",
        "answer": "We established",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "numakkin",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَأَ",
        "answer": "the chiefs",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-mala-a",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَلَئِهِ",
        "answer": "and his chiefs",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wamala-ihi",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَأُ",
        "answer": "O chiefs",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-mala-u",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَمُنَّ",
        "answer": "bestow a favor",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "namunna",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنَّ",
        "answer": "Allah had favored",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "manna",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمَنَّوْا",
        "answer": "(had) wished",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tamannaw",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَاءَ",
        "answer": "(to the) water",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "māa",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبَإِ",
        "answer": "(the) news",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "naba-i",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْبَاءُ",
        "answer": "the information",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "l-anbāu",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَبَذْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "and We threw them",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "fanabadhnāhum",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجَوْتَ",
        "answer": "You have escaped",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "najawta",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجِّنِي",
        "answer": "Save me",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "najjinī",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُودِيَ",
        "answer": "he was called",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "nūdiya",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَادَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We called",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "nādaynā",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَادِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "He will call them",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "yunādīhim",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَادِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "He will call them",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "yunādīhim",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَادِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "He will call them",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yunādīhim",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتُنْذِرَ",
        "answer": "so that you warn",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "litundhira",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَذِيرٍ",
        "answer": "warner",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "nadhīrin",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَزَعْنَا",
        "answer": "And We will draw forth",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wanazaʿnā",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْتَ",
        "answer": "You send",
        "pcklId": "206",
        "tlit": "anzalta",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَتْ",
        "answer": "they have been revealed",
        "pcklId": "207",
        "tlit": "unzilat",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِسَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their women",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "nisāahum",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْسَ",
        "answer": "forget",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "tansa",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْشَأْنَا",
        "answer": "[We] produced",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "anshanā",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصِيبَكَ",
        "answer": "your share",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "naṣībaka",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَاصِحُونَ",
        "answer": "(will be) sincere",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "nāṣiḥūna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاصِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the sincere advisors",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-nāṣiḥīna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْصَرُونَ",
        "answer": "they will be helped",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "yunṣarūna",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْصُرُونَهُ",
        "answer": "(to) help him",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yanṣurūnahu",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَنْصَرَهُ",
        "answer": "sought his help",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "is'tanṣarahu",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنْتَصِرِينَ",
        "answer": "those who (could) defend themselves",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "l-muntaṣirīna",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَانْظُرْ",
        "answer": "So see",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "fa-unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْعَمْتَ",
        "answer": "You have favored",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "anʿamta",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسِي",
        "answer": "my soul",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "nafsī",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسًا",
        "answer": "a person",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "nafsan",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسًا",
        "answer": "a man",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "nafsan",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْفَعَنَا",
        "answer": "he may benefit us",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yanfaʿanā",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنْفِقُونَ",
        "answer": "they spend",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "yunfiqūna",
        "frequency": "111",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْكِحَكَ",
        "answer": "marry you to",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "unkiḥaka",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّهَارَ",
        "answer": "the day",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-nahāra",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنَّهَارَ",
        "answer": "and the day",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "wal-nahāra",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَنُوءُ",
        "answer": "would burden",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "latanūu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَارًا",
        "answer": "a fire",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "nāran",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَارًا",
        "answer": "a fire",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "nāran",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "the fire",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "men",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for the mankind",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَاتُوا",
        "answer": "Bring",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "hātū",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِيَنِي",
        "answer": "will guide me",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "yahdiyanī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "tahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guides",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْتَدُونَ",
        "answer": "guided",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "yahtadūna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْدَىٰ",
        "answer": "(is) a better guide",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "ahdā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "with [the] guidance",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "bil-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَهُدًى",
        "answer": "and a guidance",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "wahudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدًى",
        "answer": "guidance",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "hudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "the guidance",
        "pcklId": "258",
        "tlit": "l-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "with the guidance",
        "pcklId": "259",
        "tlit": "bil-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمُهْتَدِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the guided ones",
        "pcklId": "309",
        "tlit": "bil-muh'tadīna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَهْتَزُّ",
        "answer": "moving",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tahtazzu",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَكْنَا",
        "answer": "We had destroyed",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "ahlaknā",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَكْنَا",
        "answer": "We have destroyed",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "ahlaknā",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَكَ",
        "answer": "destroyed",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "ahlaka",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُهْلِكِي",
        "answer": "(the) one to destroy",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "muh'likī",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَالِكٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) destroyed",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "hālikun",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُهْلِكَ",
        "answer": "(the) one to destroy",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "muh'lika",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْوَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their desires",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ahwāahum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَوَاهُ",
        "answer": "his own desire",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "hawāhu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوَجَدَ",
        "answer": "and found",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "fawajada",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَدَ",
        "answer": "he found",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "wajada",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَوَجَدَ",
        "answer": "and he found",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "wawajada",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَتَجِدُنِي",
        "answer": "You will find me",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "satajidunī",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَجَّهَ",
        "answer": "he turned his face",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "tawajjaha",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجْهَهُ",
        "answer": "His Face",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "wajhahu",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَوْحَيْنَا",
        "answer": "And We inspired",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "wa-awḥaynā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَادِ",
        "answer": "(of) the valley ",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-wādi",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَارِثِينَ",
        "answer": "the inheritors",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "l-wārithīna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَارِثِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) the inheritors",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-wārithīna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَدَ",
        "answer": "he came",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "warada",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصِلُونَ",
        "answer": "they will reach",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yaṣilūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "We have conveyed",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "waṣṣalnā",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَدْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We have promised him",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "waʿadnāhu",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعْدَ",
        "answer": "the Promise of Allah",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "waʿda",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعْدًا",
        "answer": "a promise",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "waʿdan",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَوْقِدْ",
        "answer": "So kindle",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "fa-awqid",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "(is) for the righteous",
        "pcklId": "240",
        "tlit": "lil'muttaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوَكَزَهُ",
        "answer": "so Musa struck him with his fist",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fawakazahu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكِيلٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a Witness",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "wakīlun",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَدًا",
        "answer": "(as) a son",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "waladan",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَّىٰ",
        "answer": "he turned",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wallā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَلَّىٰ",
        "answer": "he turned back",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "tawallā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَكَ",
        "answer": "your hand",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "yadaka",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hands",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَمِّ",
        "answer": "the river",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-yami",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَمِّ",
        "answer": "the sea",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-yami",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَيْمَنِ",
        "answer": "the right",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-aymani",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "and (on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "wayawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "and (on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "wayawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "And (the) Day",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "wayawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "And (the) Day",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "wayawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) Day",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) Day",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "And (the) Day",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "wayawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "28",
        "ayah": "74"
    }
]; 
export default words;